10kto1mm.com 2018-05-11

# 10Kto1MM.com - Privacy Policy

 ** Privacy**  

At **10KTO1MM.com** , we are committed to protecting your privacy. Whenever we collect personal information from you, we will always explain to you how we intend to use that information. For example, we will use the information you give us to process your requests and transactions, or to provide you with information about relevant products and services..

**10KTO1MM.com** will not share or sell information regarding its customers and/or prospective customers.

**10KTO1MM.com** may disclose information regarding Customer and Customer's transactions to federal or state regulatory agencies and law enforcement authorities in response to a request for such information or in response to a court order or subpoena.

We emphasize to our employees the confidential nature of user information and the high level of importance we place on maintaining this confidentiality. Furthermore, any companies we hire to provide support services must comply with our privacy policies.

We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any other web site, including sites to which we provide a link for informational purposes.

You agree that by submiting your testimonials in video, image, or text, you give us consent to use your materials.

**USE OF COOKIES**

We do not use cookies at this time. "Cookies" are small amounts of data that a Web site can send to your Web browser and store on your computer. Cookies do not contain personal information about you (unless you knowingly provide it).

**UPDATES**

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

Privacy Policy   |   Terms & Conditions   |   Secure Shopping   |    Risk Disclosure

Copyright © 2010 10KTO1MM.COM. All Rights Reserved
